Christmas with a Prince is a drama, romance, tv
movie film directed by Justin G. Dyck.
Pediatric specialist Tasha Mason is focused on one thing; keeping the
kids in her ward as healthy and happy as possible.
So when her high-school crush, who just happens to be handsome Prince Alexander Cavalieri, breaks his leg on a nearby ski-slope, Tasha is forced to allow him
to secretly get well on her floor and she’s furious that a spoiled Royal is interrupting the precious healing time her kids so badly need.
Soon, however, Tasha learns that some tough love and a lot of Christmas
spirit, could turn this royal pain into a knight in shining armor.
Dr. Tasha Miller, played by Kaitlyn Leeb.
Prince Alexander, played by Nick Hounslow.
Jeff, played by Josh Dean.
Bella, played by Melinda Shankar.
King Edward, played by Charles Shaughnessy.
Ben, played by Liam MacDonald.
A Christmas Prince is a 2017 Christmas romantic comedy film directed by Alex Zamm, written by Karen Schaler and Nathan Atkins,
and stars Rose McIver, Ben Lamb, Tom Knight, Sarah Douglas, Daniel Fathers, Alice Krige, and Tahirah Sharif.
The film was released on Netflix on November 17, 2017.
Two sequels, A Christmas Prince: The Royal Wedding, &, A
Christmas Prince: The Royal Baby came out a year apart.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, royalty, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.